

Mahdi Parastesh

Full-Stack Software Engineer

I have 5 years of experience in developing Android apps and 4 years in Full-Stack development along with Flutter. The programming languages I'm skilled at are JavaScript, PHP, Java, Kotlin, Dart, Python and C++. I develop Android apps using mere Java/Kotlin, or also for iOS using Flutter.

fulcrum522@hotmail.com

Abhar, Zanjan, Iran

in linkedin.com/in/fulcrum6378

github.com/fulcrum6378

+989196658766

mahdiparastesh.ir

live:.cid.6a5e817b54226bd6

🖹 stackoverflow.com/users/10728785/mahdi-parastesh

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android App Publisher

Google Play Store, Galaxy Store, Bazaar and Myket

12/2021 - 09/2022 Myket: Mahdi Parastesh

Remote Full-Stack Developer

Freelancer

07/2020 - 07/2021 Gosport, UK

Full-Time Android Developer Technofast Automation Iraa

02/2020 - 01/2021

Qom, Iran https://tecfas.com/

Front-End Developer

Freelancer

06/2013 - 08/2014 Qom, Iran

EDUCATION (100% SELF-TAUGHT)

W3 Schools

https://www.w3schools.com/

07/2012 - 07/2021

Android Developers

https://developer.android.com/

08/2018 - 05/2021

Flutter Docs

https://flutter.dev/docs

06/2020 - 08/2022

Python Docs

https://www.python.org/

12/2020 - 07/2021

SKILLS



PROJECTS

InstaTools (11/2021 - Present)

- Instagram Downloader, Unfollower Finder, Saver and Direct Message Viewer and Exporter
- https://myket.ir/app/ir.mahdiparastesh.instatools

Telexporter (01/2021 - Present)

- SMS and Call History Exporter; it supports exporting into HTML web page, PDF document and TXT file formats
- https://cafebazaar.ir/app/ir.mahdiparastesh.telexporter

Migratio (05/2020 - 10/2020)

- A statistical geographical app designed in Android and Web for determining someone's best destination for migration
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=ir.mahdiparastesh.migratio

CERTIFICATES

Android and Java certification (07/2020)

https://app.testdome.com/cert/1bac69cf357f4cb5b3c73b279b78be26

LANGUAGES

Persian English

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Machine Learning **Computer Vision**

Neuroscience